I didn't write down the last one I
stopped because I have frog in my throat
and now there's a whole new idea there
and I can always go back to that one
because it's one of my tried-and-true
ones but I can't believe I've got nearly
50% of the way and haven't talked about
it yet but another time so I've never
been very sporty I don't haven't played
organized sports besides I was on a team
of Ultimate Frisbee when I was at UBC
and even then I'm not so sure I was
great at showing up for games and I
definitely was one of the best people on
a team but I do like playing certain
sports like kick-the-can
that's about it as a sports marketing
but having neighborhood game nights
where you're able to use the local park
and anyone can come and play sign up in
advance and it's free or very low cost
or grants are used for it and to be able
to facilitate that online of course so
that anyone who's like hey I'd like it
can be an actual sport so soccer or
baseball anything that you want to get
together and play but even of all
generations all say all ages that comes
generation joy but diversity you don't
need to necessarily speak the language
to play a game but that would be
important to at least let the colleg in
someone's language that you're more than
welcome and even more importantly I
think it would be fun to have people
make up games and say hey I'm meant to
this game wanna come out and learn it
and play it with me I think that would
just be really fun and awkward and weird
and that's part of what makes it fun and
I love that so that is Apple number 47
is to help people facilitate
neighborhood games